http://www.magdrl.org/privacy-statement

f t r
Email Us
The Mid-Atlantic Great Dane Rescue League, Inc.
Search
Go »
Favorite Links
Home »
Privacy Statement The Mid-Atlantic Great Dane Rescue League, Inc. (MAGDRL) is committed to your right to privacy and to keeping your personal information private.
You can visit the MAGDRL web site without telling us who you are or revealing any identifying information about yourself. However, because our web site includes areas in which visitors can provide personally identifying information, we have developed this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and practices regarding information we collect about you.
How We Use Information
Information you voluntarily provide: MAGDRL collects and maintains certain personal information about you when you complete any of our forms such as in downloadable adoption forms; or when you make a donation, subscribe to our newsletter, become a volunteer or member, or send electronic communication to us. Such information may include your name, e-mail address, or mailing address; it may also include the e-mail addresses of those to whom you forward MAGDRL electronic content, and any other information collected in the forms.
MAGDRL adheres to generally accepted Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development (OECD) guidance on use limitation which specifies that, “personal data should not be disclosed, made available or otherwise used for purposes other than those specified in accordance with the “purpose specification” except: (a) with the consent of the data subject; or (b) by the authority of the law.” MAGDRL does not buy, sell, rent or trade our contact or mailing lists.
For MAGDRL web site visitors who do not make purchases or otherwise identify themselves, our web server does not have access to personally identifiable information about you. It does not know your e-mail address unless you volunteer it.
For MAGDRL web site visitors who make donations or purchases on this site, you may be asked to provide information to our authorized secure payment authority (PayPal) to become a member, to contribute to MAGDRL, to purchase certain materials from MAGDRL, or to subscribe to publications. MAGDRL does not receive, collect or retain your financial information. Instead, PayPal collects your name, contact information, credit card or bank information, as well as information about your current purchase. Only your contact information is returned to MAGDRL to enable us to deliver your purchases, to acknowledge your donations, and to respond to questions should the need arise.
We DO NOT share your name or contact information with other companies, nonprofit organizations, or individuals without your expressed permission. MAGDRL may contact you to respond as a result of information you provided to us through our contact web site.
Other Information
MAGDRL may collect information when you visit our web sites. We may log information for system administration and to monitor the use of our site. The type of information collected may include:
The client’s Internet Protocol (IP) address, from which the domain name and the name and location of the organization who registered this domain name can be determined through the Domain Name System
Basic information about the browser, operating system and hardware platform used by the client
The time and date of the visit
The Uniform Resource Locator (URL) of the Web page which was viewed immediately prior to accessing the current page
If a search engine was used to find the site, the entire query may be passed on to the server
We may use the aggregated information to measure the number of visits to our site, the average time spent on our site, the number of pages viewed, and various other site statistics. This monitoring helps us to tune the performance of our system, provide a more useful and engaging online experience to MAGDRL site visitors, and help improve the quality of our content.
Cookies
A cookie is a tiny file that is sent out by a web site, accepted by the user’s browser, and placed on the user’s hard drive. Some web sites use cookies to facilitate the collection of voluntarily disclosed data.
MAGDRL does not use cookies on any of our web sites, nor do we place any files on your computer.
Links
MAGDRL has links to other web sites that may not be affiliated with us. MAGDRL attempts to link only to those web sites which also respect a visitor’s privacy and the goals of MAGDRL. However, MAGDRL cannot be responsible for the content or policies of third-party web sites. Please check with these organizations or companies for their specific privacy policies. If you find inoperable links or are concerned about any of the sites that MAGDRL currently links to, please inform MAGDRL by contacting us at webmaster@magdrl.org or write to us at MAGDRL, P.O. Box 285, Hanover, MD 21076.
Security
MAGDRL’s web sites are hosted by service providers that use generally accepted, industry-standard security systems, software, and encryption technologies to protect against unauthorized access to servers, equipment, and other components of our online presence.
Disclaimer
This site and all of the materials on or reference by the site are provided on an “as is” basis. In no event shall MAGDRL be liable for any direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, or consequential damages of any kind whatsoever with respect to the use of this site. By viewing our content, you agree that you are using this site solely at your own risk.
Contacting MAGDRL
If you would like to contact MAGDRL about correcting information we have on our web site, or if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at webmaster@magdrl.org or write to us at MAGDRL, P.O. Box 285, Hanover, MD 21076.
MAGDRL Privacy Policy
